wanttoknowit.com 2018-01-04

# Privacy Policy

* * *

**Wanttoknowit.com**

The privacy of our visitors is very important. If you have any questions or queries you may contact us via the email address in the sidebar.

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit this site, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. No personal information (name, address etc.) is collected in this process.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
As far as we are aware we are not and do not plan on using cookies for this site.

However, we do use third party advertisements on this website to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Boston real estate ads to someone in Boston, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Our advertising partners use the DART tracking cookie to do this. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. Although all practical measures are taken to avoid conflicts with these programs using them may affect your ability to view the site as it was originally intended.
